# Chaitanya S

UI/UX designer Full-stack designer

"I am a cognitive designer with about 2+ years of experience in user experience design, 1+ in story boarding and 2+ in Auto CAD designing. . I love to work in a progressive environment where I can utilize my knowledge and experience to learn new skills and also get involved in being a part of a winning team."

# **Work Experience**

# Wongdoody + Infosys

Mar2021 - till date

Associate-experience Designer

I Delighted to worked with Fortune 500MNC, where I had chance to explored designing across a variety of domains. Meanwhile, continuously skill up through the in-house training's and initiatives.

#### • Online Banking gaint application

Working with a team of developers and designers as Full-stack designer/ UX unicorn to create online banking responsive design where my role is to collaborate with designers to create high fidelity designs and achieve the same in development.

### • Banking platform Design Syatem

Worked in Digital Banking Processing Platforms for Retail and Corporate Banking by Independent Research Firm where the responsibility is to develope what we designed

### Government TAX Agency

worked as a UX researcher to enhance user experience for mobile screens where the final outcome was 50% faster completion of form-filling task and 60%screen reduction with all functionalities compared to existing screens with zero deficiency delivery and received insta Award for best rating from client

### • DA portal

lead 2+ designers to Designed and presented native flows for a for Employee well being share-point intranet site.

### • Agriculture domain

Worked as a visual designer for design System in global agriculture white label company

## Inucom Pvt LTD

Sep2020 - Feb2021

### Story board Artist & SME

worked as a Story board artist to Creating story boards with Pen Tab to create visual impact of the story line, which help to create 3D, 2D videos making along with it worked as SME for Electrical subjects.

# M.Govind & sons

Aprl2013 - Sep2014

### Design Engineer

Responsible was to create Auto CAD Design layouts, plans, design samples for automatic bailing cotton press machines and hydraulic machines. A key achievement was pointed out design failure of tilting cotton press design and the submitted design solution on Solid works.

## **Education Qualifications**

**BFA**, Applied Arts in JNAFA University, Hyderabad (70%). **BTech**, EEE in Narasaraopet institute of technology, Guntur (75%).

Intermediate, M.P.C in G.C.SS.Jr college, Guntur (85%).

S.S.C in G.C.SS. High School, Guntur (88.2%).

2016-2020

2008-2012

2006-2008

2005-2006

### **Contact details**

chaitanyauxdesigner@gmail.com

<u>a</u>bcde@xyz.com

+91 7569496182 | 9542909009

### **Skills**

Ux research, UI design, Create personas, Information architecture, competitive analysis, high fidelity wire-frames, prototypes, HTML 5, Css3, SASS, Bootstrap, Responsive Web design.

### **Awards**

Received Insta Award at Infosys

### **Certifications**

Full-stack design certification SAP Fiori 3 design system

### **Hobbies**

Pinting

Drawing

Planting

Science Experiments

### **Tools**

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe illustrator

Adobe sketchbook

Procreate

AutoCADD

Appzillon3.10

Miro